Tufts Literary Magazine UP014
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts Literary Magazine
1966 -- 1974
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Literary Magazine of Tufts University
UP014
0.25 Linear Feet
2 Volumes
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Custodial History
Tufts Literary Magazine was a student literary publication of prose and poetry.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains bound and unbound issues of the Tufts Literary Magazine from 1966 through 1974. It was originally published biannually and then annually starting in 1969.
Biographical / Historical
The Literary Magazine was seen as a new literary enterprise that broke away from previous publications. This student group formed in 1966. Exact date the group disbanded is unknown.
- Tufts Literary Magazine, 1966 -- 1974; UP014.001; 0.25 Linear Feet; 2 Volumes
  Scope and Contents
  Tufts Literary Magazine was a student literary publication of prose and poetry.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Literary Magazine of Tufts University, Winter, 1968; UP014.001.001.00005 (Box Volume 1)
  - Literary Magazine of Tufts University, 1968; UP014.001.001.00006 (Box Volume 1)
  - Literary Magazine of Tufts University, 1969; UP014.001.002.00001 (Box Volume 2)
    Volume, issue
    4, 1
  - Literary Magazine of Tufts University, 1970; UP014.001.002.00002 (Box Volume 2)
    5, 1
  - Literary Magazine of Tufts University, 1971; UP014.001.002.00003 (Box Volume 2)
    6, 1
  - Literary Magazine of Tufts University, 1971; UP014.001.002.00004 (Box Volume 2)
    6, 2
  - Tufts Literary Magazine, 1972; UP014.001.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - Tufts Literary Magazine, 1973; UP014.001.003.00002 (Box 3)
  - Tufts Literary Magazine, 1974; UP014.001.003.00003 (Box 3)
  - Tufts Literary Magazine, Spring, 1966; UP014.001.003.00004 (Box 3)
    1, 2